Records of the National Society Of New England Women, 1895-1988
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- MEMORABILIA AND OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Oversize Materials
    - Colonies
      - Evanston, IL Colony
        - General, scrapbooks, 1968-1972
          - 1972-1973 (Box 106)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 106)
          - 1975-1977 (Box 106)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 106)
      - Philadelphia, PA Colony
        - General, scrapbook, 1917-1940
          - 1950-1951 (Box 106)